We drink this money in a bar. We take
girls out. We do shopping. And over the
weekend, we finished a two or 3 million
shillings at
once. I'm Elizabeth Nagir
Najuma, an executive financial advisor
from Prodential Life Assurance Uganda.
My passion and purpose mainly is
serving. I love serving people. I love
people. I love to know that people are
fine. For Uganda to be one of the best
developed countries, we need to start a
a culture that is going to make us
better tomorrow, the other day and the
other day. So, one of my first clients
uh we met somewhere in a restaurant. So,
we are here jing this is good for your
family, this is good for you, this the
so asks a question to a friend. Why do
you think I should take up this policy?
So the friend says, "Man, you need this.
You need this." We drink this money in a
bar. We take girls out. We do shopping.
And over the weekend, we finished two or
3 million shillings at once. So a client
takes up a policy of 2 million shillings
monthly. And 4 months uh down the road,
he had his 8 million shillings on his
account already. and he's like, "Man,
please this is very good. I have my 8
million saved up aside for my children's
future." And by the end of the year, he
has made a year already. He has almost
26 million saved up for his future. So
that is one of the experiences that has
kept me pushing knowing that insurance
is actually the real deal because you
know life is unpredictable. Today you're
well, tomorrow you're not. Today you're
sick, the other day you're fine. But we
do not predict this kind of things in
life. So choose wisely. Choose
insurance. Take up a policy today with
credential and secure the future of your
loved ones. Together we can do it to
Linawi.
[Music]